[Music]
hello hello everybody I'm your host
Diego Luca and welcome to Buenas Buenas
Buenas
NES please down no please please thank
you thank you we have an amazing show
for you tonight but first did you hear
about this very very interesting now
apparently Disney is coming out with a
new musical yes it involves a lot of
white people on skates apparently
they're calling it
hockey
oh am I right please oh now it's time
for one of our favorite segments
stinging on motorcycles in traffic now
today's guest is none other than
two-time Academy Award winner Daniel de
leis let's see how we
did
oh my goodness so good I would even say
sharable am I right seriously share it
please share it share it share it right
now click at the bottom click on
it okay it's time to introduce our very
special friend you know him it is Kevin
the IT guy hi hello
not accent I mean who can understand oh
now Kevin tell us tell the folks at home
what did you do this weekend Oh I made
my own dinner ooh interesting what did
you have uh Craisins MH uh asparagus mhm
and uh I make my own
Selter again I'm again you are different
from me and that is funny to us H now
after all that dinner I think that Kevin
could lose a few calories so it's time
for
Kevin learns how to do
things oh my goodness now with the help
of our lovely and talented sopia today
we are going to teach Kevin how to dance
come on out
Kevin uh is this outfit necessary all
putting you down makes me look better
huh take it away Sophia we're going to
do the Bachata today here we go we go to
the
[Applause]
right hey
fire it looks like Kevin was really
feeling it let's take a look at the
replay you look so stupid but how great
was Sophia am I right give her a round
of applause
please now as many of you know next week
I will be on vacation have a good trip
oh thank you don't tell my
wife no she knows she knows know but I'm
very excited to announce who's going to
be filling in for me next week now one
of the most talented comedians I know so
funny she's one of the most F
no no I don't want that or it can be any
guy any guy any guy oh man that was
close that was a lot of fun almost as
fun as our band leader the the the DJ
man I already told you I'm not in the
van I'm Steve the script supervisor you
think I'm the DJ because I'm the only
black guy here
yes well we're not done with the fun
just yet now throughout the night we've
been telling Kevin that he's going to a
cooking show when in reality we're
sending him to meet notorious drug lord
El what
no
[Applause]
have a great
trip oh my God you're going to love
him now tune in next week when a famous
actress pretends to find me Charming in
order to plug her movie and until then
bu
[Music]
bu all right get me out of this
place thank
[Music]
you